Guide to the Honors Committee, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Honors Committee, Yale College, records
1910-1928
RU 539
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
The records consist of correspondence, examinations, news clippings, and courses of study documenting the activities of the Yale College Honors Committee.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-D (YRG 9-D), Records of Yale College committees.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, examinations, news clippings, and courses of study documenting the activities of the Yale College Honors Committee.
Universities and colleges -- Curricula; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Curricula
- Records, 1910-1928; Accession 1945-A-001
  - Old honors scheme, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - First scheme and news articles, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Circular to departments, replies, analysis, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - News article, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Day & Fairchild's suggestion -minutes of meetings, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Revised plan, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty meeting, 1914 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Replies from departments, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Honors - old plan, 1914-1916 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Honors plan at other institutions, 1913-1916 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Examinations, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations, 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Examinations, 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1920-1923 (Box 1, Folder 16 - 17)
  - Correspondence, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Honors course of study, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 19)